[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "But what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, it's been a chaotic year.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "chaotic", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What did you think of that choice?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "that", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "ROKAW: I thought it was a good call, frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["ROKAW", ":", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "good", "call", ",", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "I mean, is there -- is there a common thread there or are they very different, distinct protests?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "there", "--", "is", "there", "a", "common", "thread", "there", "or", "are", "they", "very", "different", ",", "distinct", "protests", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, I think it's a very different -- first of all, Occupy Wall Street is not calling for the overthrow of their government.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "different", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Occupy", "Wall", "Street", "is", "not", "calling", "for", "the", "overthrow", "of", "their", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What kind of future young Americans going to be facing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "future", "young", "Americans", "going", "to", "be", "facing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, first of all, I was a member of the luckiest generation as my contemporaries -- and we've all agreed that we were the ones who really caught the best wave, because after the war, our parents who had gone through all the trials of the Depression and World War II, then came home to unprecedented working class and middle class prosperity.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "was", "a", "member", "of", "the", "luckiest", "generation", "as", "my", "contemporaries", "--", "and", "we", "'ve", "all", "agreed", "that", "we", "were", "the", "ones", "who", "really", "caught", "the", "best", "wave", ",", "because", "after", "the", "war", ",", "our", "parents", "who", "had", "gone", "through", "all", "the", "trials", "of", "the", "Depression", "and", "World", "War", "II", ",", "then", "came", "home", "to", "unprecedented", "working", "class", "and", "middle", "class", "prosperity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "What do you make of the way the Republican race is going, the debates in particular?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "way", "the", "Republican", "race", "is", "going", ",", "the", "debates", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "ROKAW: Well, I frankly I'm a big advocate of as many debates as we can have along primary seasons because you find out about candidates during that time.", "answer_tokens": ["ROKAW", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "frankly", "I", "'m", "a", "big", "advocate", "of", "as", "many", "debates", "as", "we", "can", "have", "along", "primary", "seasons", "because", "you", "find", "out", "about", "candidates", "during", "that", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "And is it unfeasible that someone like him could actually come from a very low base and still win the nomination?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "unfeasible", "that", "someone", "like", "him", "could", "actually", "come", "from", "a", "very", "low", "base", "and", "still", "win", "the", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, I think he has some hopes that he can do that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "has", "some", "hopes", "that", "he", "can", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"], "LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "If he can do well in Iowa and then at least be in the hunt in New Hampshire, then goes out to South Carolina, and then go to Florida, who knows?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "can", "do", "well", "in", "Iowa", "and", "then", "at", "least", "be", "in", "the", "hunt", "in", "New", "Hampshire", ",", "then", "goes", "out", "to", "South", "Carolina", ",", "and", "then", "go", "to", "Florida", ",", "who", "knows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "I mean, what you could have -- judging by the polls at the moment -- you could have Ron Paul winning in Iowa.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "you", "could", "have", "--", "judging", "by", "the", "polls", "at", "the", "moment", "--", "you", "could", "have", "Ron", "Paul", "winning", "in", "Iowa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa", "New Hampshire", "South Carolina", "Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "What did you have against that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "have", "against", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I didn't have any -- listen, I didn't have anything against -- I have known Donald Trump for a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "--", "listen", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "have", "anything", "against", "--", "I", "have", "known", "Donald", "Trump", "for", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Has he been on balance more of a success than a failure?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "been", "on", "balance", "more", "of", "a", "success", "than", "a", "failure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think it's very -- very hard to judge the greatness of a president midterm and that's kind of where we are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "--", "very", "hard", "to", "judge", "the", "greatness", "of", "a", "president", "midterm", "and", "that", "'s", "kind", "of", "where", "we", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Who do you think has been the most impressive of all of them?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "has", "been", "the", "most", "impressive", "of", "all", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "You know, you're not going to trap me into that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "trap", "me", "into", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "When you saw President Obama really trying to make it that it had been a victory and it had all been worth it, did you agree with him?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "President", "Obama", "really", "trying", "to", "make", "it", "that", "it", "had", "been", "a", "victory", "and", "it", "had", "all", "been", "worth", "it", ",", "did", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, what I think is -- and I think it's a complex question, by the way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "think", "is", "--", "and", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "complex", "question", ",", "by", "the", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NATO"]}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What do you think about the changing manner in which American military is now deploying itself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "changing", "manner", "in", "which", "American", "military", "is", "now", "deploying", "itself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "JJ", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "That was an easier call for the involvement of the American military as part of NATO force.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "an", "easier", "call", "for", "the", "involvement", "of", "the", "American", "military", "as", "part", "of", "NATO", "force", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Wouldn't it be better to say we're going to tackle terrorism head on, and actually treat Afghanistan, rather than a war, as an anti-terrorism operation?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "it", "be", "better", "to", "say", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "tackle", "terrorism", "head", "on", ",", "and", "actually", "treat", "Afghanistan", ",", "rather", "than", "a", "war", ",", "as", "an", "anti-terrorism", "operation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, it's -- war should not be reduced to a semantic exercise of some kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "war", "should", "not", "be", "reduced", "to", "a", "semantic", "exercise", "of", "some", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Besher"]}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VBG", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Any regrets over the green jacket, Tom, looking back on that?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "regrets", "over", "the", "green", "jacket", ",", "Tom", ",", "looking", "back", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I had to trade jackets later with one of my colleague, Mike Besher (ph), because I got to thinking, this is probably going to be on videotape for a long time, and I ought to get dressed up a little more.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "to", "trade", "jackets", "later", "with", "one", "of", "my", "colleague", ",", "Mike", "Besher", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "because", "I", "got", "to", "thinking", ",", "this", "is", "probably", "going", "to", "be", "on", "videotape", "for", "a", "long", "time", ",", "and", "I", "ought", "to", "get", "dressed", "up", "a", "little", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "When you look at all the incredible things that you've witnessed, Tom, over the last few decades, which to you is the standout moment, the one that if you had the chance to relive it and to be there again, you would take?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "all", "the", "incredible", "things", "that", "you", "'ve", "witnessed", ",", "Tom", ",", "over", "the", "last", "few", "decades", ",", "which", "to", "you", "is", "the", "standout", "moment", ",", "the", "one", "that", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "to", "relive", "it", "and", "to", "be", "there", "again", ",", "you", "would", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, I don't want to relive some of them, because the single hardest week I had, and the single hardest day by far, was 9/11.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "relive", "some", "of", "them", ",", "because", "the", "single", "hardest", "week", "I", "had", ",", "and", "the", "single", "hardest", "day", "by", "far", ",", "was", "9/11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Are you still a complete news junkie?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "still", "a", "complete", "news", "junkie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]